人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十四集
蒂娜  快 罗夏墨迹测验  开始
Tina, quick, Rorschach test, go.
对墨渍图案反应而分析性格的实验
演《猫屎先生》的格雷戈・金尼尔
Um, Greg Kinnear from As Good as It Gets?
没错
Yes, wow.
小点声  我在和银行的人通电话
Shh, shh, I'm on the phone with the bank.
好  把付给电力公司的支票退了
Okay, so bounce the check to the power company,
付给开胃菜供应商的也退了
bounce the check to the relish guy,
但要确保牛肉供应商的支票能兑
but make sure the beef supplier goes through.
没有牛肉  餐馆就没法运作了
Without beef, the whole system falls apart.
至少我床上的牛肉是免费供应的
Yeah, at least my bedroom beef supply is free.
"beef"作为俚语有"放屁"的意思
没错
Yeah.
谢了  马尔西  你是我们的救命恩人
Thanks, Marci. You're a lifesaver.
回头再谈  亲爱的
I'll talk to you later, honey.
天哪  真不敢相信我们在操控银行退票
God, I can't believe we're doing controlled bounces,
我也不敢相信你竟然那样跟银行的人讲话
and I can't believe you talk that way to the bank.
咋了  你说马尔西吗
Oh, what, with Marci?
没关系啦  我们之间没有秘密
It's okay. We don't have any secrets.
她丈夫去年重新割了包皮
You know, her husband had to get recircumcised last year.
以前的又长回来了
The first one grew back.
-那玩意才不会长回来  -可他就长了
- They don't grow back. - Somehow it did.
大老爷们儿了还得行哥礼  有够奇怪的
They had to have an adult "Brisk"; it was freaky.
不是"哥礼"  是"割礼"
It's not a brisk; it's a bris.
蛤蜊来蛤蜊去的  我都饿了
All this brisket talk is making me hungry.
你把账簿弄成这样干嘛  你逻辑好混乱
And why do you do the books this way? Your system is crazy.
那是我们勉强维生的唯一办法  亲爱的
It's the only way to keep our heads above water, my love.
那我们就得想办法减少开支了
Well, then, we've got to find a way to cut down on expenses.
有什么是我们没有也能过活的
What can we live without?
-也许是吉恩和蒂娜  -继续
- Uh, probably Gene and Tina. - That's a good start.
我本来也觉得我俩是可有可无的人
Huh, well, it makes the things I was gonna cut irrelevant.
很好
Good.
这样吧  我去做兼职
You know what? I could get a part-time job.
什么
Huh, what?
不  琳  我们还没到那一步
No, Lin, it hasn't come to that yet.
是  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
有了  从今天起
Hey, maybe I'll start shopping
我去上街那边的鲜食超市买东西
at that Fresh Feed place up the street.
听说那里非常便宜
I hear it's really cheap.
对啊  这主意不错
Oh, yeah, that's good.
那儿有花生酱小甜甜圈
They have those peanut butter mini donuts.
我更喜欢淋酸奶的花生酱小甜甜圈
I prefer the yogurt-covered peanut butter mini donuts,
但老妈  我口味可是很挑的哦
but, hey, I have a refined palette.
挑  你连自己的腋窝都舔
Refined? You lick your own armpits.
那儿有天然的香辣味嘛
They're naturally spicy.
鲜食超市
"让你因坚果而疯狂"
"People go nuts for our nuts."
"nuts"为多义词  可指"坚果"  也有"疯狂"的意思
真搞笑  我喜欢
What a hoot. I love it.
"急着买咖喱吗"
"In a hurry for some curry?"
有一点吧
Hmm, kind of.
伙计  每位顾客一份
Hey, buddy, one sample per customer.
一人份包含四个小鸡蛋卷
A serving size is four mini egg rolls.
也就是说  四块等于一份
Therefore, four pieces equals one sample.
祝你过得愉快  先生
Good day, sir.
牛奶后面好像有人
I think there's someone behind the milk.
也许是牛奶小精灵
Maybe it's a dairy fairy.
或是一个跟踪狂在用他可怖冷酷的眼睛
Or a stalker watching our every move
监视着我们的一举一动
with their creepy frozen eyes.
你好
Hi.
真是便宜到爆啊
Look at these crazy low prices.
-抱歉  -请叫我格雷格
- Excuse me. - Greg.
你好  格雷格
Uh, hi, Greg.
能告诉我葡萄酒在哪儿吗
Yeah, can you tell me where the wine is?
你是说大人喝的葡萄汁啊
Ah, the grown-up grape juice.
跟我来看看我们的葡萄园吧
Come with me to our vineyard.
用塑料瓶盛的酒  有意思
Ooh, wine in a squeeze bottle. Fun.
迪斯科时间到了
It's time for a disco minute.
要跳多久
How long's it last?
一小会
A minute.
在这里工作一定很棒
It must be great working here.
没错  很有乐子
Yup, we have fun.
这是我们的特色
It's kind of our thing.
我喜欢有特色的地方
I love it when a place has a thing.
工作时间还很灵活
And the hours are flexible,
对于像我这样的人来说再适合不过了
which is fantastic for someone like me.
要知道风和日丽的天气
You never know when the perfect breeze
总是可遇而不可求的
is going to blow.
我还有份职业是风筝放飞员
I'm a semipro kite pilot.
啥  我没明白
A what? I don't understand.
哪部分你没明白
What part do you not understand?
你的用词  我不太理解
The words-- I don't understand them.
我是风筝放飞员
I'm a kite pilot.
风筝放飞员
Kite pilot.
这些都是我的宝贝
Mm-hmm, my babies.
好吧
Okay.
很不错
Wow, that's great.
这么说这里的时间是很灵活的了
So there's flexible hours here, huh?
怎么感觉这变成了一场面试
Hey, did this just become a job interview?
你有兴趣吗
You interested?
我吗  什么  不
Me? What? No.
不  我不知道  我不能  不
No, I don't know, I couldn't -- no...
猜猜谁在鲜食超市找了份工作
Guess who got a job at Fresh Feed.
来听听
Check it out.
老妈要在收银台做事了
That's what Mom will be doing at the checkout.
是的  要纸袋还是塑料袋  老妈
Yeah, paper or plastic, Mom?
-我说的对吗  -正确
- Am I right? - All right.
什么  你找了一份工作
What, you got a job?
但我们还没有到那个地步  记得吗
But it hasn't come to that yet, remember?
我想老妈想说的是
I think what Mom's trying to say is:
老娘不在这儿干了  鲍勃
"Take this job and shove it, Bob!"
是的  我现在开始挣钱养家了
Yeah, I'm bringing home the bacon now.
我忘了买培根了
Oh, I forgot to get bacon.
快回去
We have to go back!
你今早还真起床了
You really got out of bed this morning.
我都等不及了
I couldn't wait!
第一天上班  好激动哦
Oh, I'm so freaking excited about my first day on the job!
你洗澡的时候
Yeah, I heard you the first time,
我已经听你这么唱过了
when you were singing in the shower.
第一天上班
I'm so freaking excited
我好激动哦
about my first day on the job.
肥皂进眼睛里了
Yeah! Ow, ow! Soap in my eye!
你终于脱身了  老妈  千万别回头
You finally got out, Mom. Don't look back.
这只是份兼职  别那么夸张
It's only part-time. Don't be so dramatic.
我只是为了挽救这个家庭
It's just something I'm doing to save the family.
没什么大不了的
No big deal.
-你好  格雷格  -你好  琳达
- Hey, Greg! - Hey, Linda.
带我转转  参观参观
Show me around. Give me the tour.
好吧  还挺有冲劲啊
Okay. A little pushy there.
那是饮水机吗
Ooh, is that a water cooler?
天哪  这下我也可以像电视上演的那样
Oh, God, I'm gonna be gossiping around
围在饮水机周围聊八卦了
a real water cooler like on TV!
我太喜欢了
I love it.
这边是面包区  这是米奇
This is the bread aisle. There's Mitch.
他组建了一个山寨米勒乐队
He's in a Steve Miller Band cover band.
米勒乐队:以史蒂夫・米勒为成员之一的摇滚乐队
有人叫你太空牛仔吗
Hey, does anyone call you the Space Cowboy?
《太空牛仔》为乐队大热单曲
有  但现在我是"面包流氓"
Yeah, but right now I'm the Gangster of Loaves.
乐队有一首歌的歌名为《爱情流氓》
说得好  米奇  越来越好笑了
Good one, Mitch! They get funnier every time.
农产品区的小虫子可真多
It's a little buggy in produce.
是的  看来苍蝇也爱水果啊
Yeah, turns out flies like fruit.
谢谢你指出这一点
Thanks for pointing that out, though.
没有琳达你怎么忙得过来  鲍勃
How you gonna get by without Linda, Bob?
她只是去做份兼职  我应付得过来
She's only working part-time. I'll be fine.
琳达告诉你怎么用恒温器了吗
Did Linda show you how to work the thermostat?
我没动过它啊
It's the same as it always is.
不对
No.
琳达能控制厨房外的温度  烤架的温度
Linda accounts for outside temperature, grill temperature,
还有客人的数量
the number of customers in here.
琳达能像拉小提琴一样自如地控制恒温器
Linda can play that thermostat like a violin.
被你这么一说 我好像真的出汗了
Now that you mention it, I do feel a little shvitzy.
我也是  得脱掉衬衫了
Oh, me, too. Shirt's coming off.
好吧  我调小点
Fine, I'll turn it down.
琳达可不是那么做的  鲍鲍
That's not how Linda does it, Bobby.
你调过头了  现在我们都得冻死了
You overshot it. Now we're all gonna freeze.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我只是调了大概两度的样子  泰迪
I moved it, like, two degrees, Teddy.
两度就能要人命了
Two degrees is everything.
就是这么两度的差别让恐龙灭绝了
Two degrees killed the dinosaurs!
好吧  我调回来
Fine! I'll move it back!
又过了
Too far again.
还得脱掉
That's got to come off!
今天你先做点轻松的适应一下
We're gonna start you off nice and easy today.
这是低于十样商品的收银台
On the ten-items-or-less register.
如果拿了十一样  给不给结账你决定
If they have 11, ban 'em or scan 'em. Your call.
我来决定  好吧  我说了算
Oh, my call! Okay. I'm in charge.
也不能全算
To a point.
请注意  有人丢猴子了吗
Excuse me, did someone lose a monkey?
我看好你
You're gonna do just fine here.
既然琳达不在
Hey, with Linda gone,
我们可以聊聊猥琐的话题
we can get into some raunchy locker room talk.
用一部电影片名来形容我们的"蛋蛋"
Hey, let's describe our testicles with a movie title.
啥
What?
《野战群》
The Wild Bunch!
等等  这是在做什么
Wait a minute. What are we doing?
《飞越疯人院》
One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest.
你只有一颗蛋吗
You have one testicle?
你知道的
You knew that.
鲍勃  这里可真热
Hey, Bob. Whoa. It's warm in here.
是的  我知道  麦克  多谢了
Yes, I know, Mike. Thanks.
琳达找了份兼职
Linda got a part-time job.
泰迪  身材不错
Teddy, you're looking good.
我不敢说
Uh... I don't know.
你有很多账单
You got a lot of bills here.
全是账单
It's all bills.
你们该付付账单了
You guys should pay your bills.
-麦克真聪明  -没错
- Mike's smart. - Yup.
我们在聊猥琐的话题
Hey, we're doing locker room talk.
-跟我们聊聊你的"蛋蛋"  -再见
- Tell us about your testicles. - Good-bye.
琳达在摆玉米货架  她并不觉得丢脸
Linda stocked corn and she don't care
Linda stocked corn and she don't care...
因为她还有西红柿切块
'Cause she's also got diced tomatoes.
罐头不错  小姐
Hey nice cans, lady.
孩子们  你们是来看妈咪的新工作的吗
Kids! You came to see Mommy at her new job?
来吧  给我的家庭成员
Come on. I'll introduce my home family
介绍一下我的工作团队成员
to my new work family.
杰米  这是我的孩子
Hey, Jamie, these are my kids.
孩子们  这是你们新哥哥  杰米
Kids, this is your new brother, Jamie.
你们好
Hey, what's up?
你们接着转吧  老妈
Go ahead with the tour, Mother.
我要和杰米一起参观
I'm going to visit with James.
没错  我现在也是鲜食大家庭的一员了
That's right, I'm part of the Fresh Feed family now,
就用不着使牙签了
so don't bother with the toothpicks.
那样太慢了
They just slow me down.
谁想要汽球
Who wants a balloon?
事实上  我想要很多的汽球
Actually, I would like many balloons.
我要做一件好多年前就该做的事情
I'm gonna do something I should've done years ago.
你能不能带我去乳品冰柜那边参观一下
I was hoping you could take me on a tour of the dairy fridge.
当然可以  宝贝  跟我来
Oh, yeah. Sure, honey. Yeah. Come on.
热门促销 冷冻虾仁 只要8块9毛9
去吧  自由的飞吧
Ooh! Go! Be free!
你们可以飘上好多天
You'll float for a few days!
也许能飞一周呢  谁知道呢
Maybe a week. Who knows?
至少你们能活下去
But you'll live.
你们能活了
You'll live!
我好像在百老汇后台看一场
Wow. It's like I'm backstage at a Broadway show...
关于买牛奶的人的演出
about people who buy milk.
听着都想看呢
Ooh, I'd see that show --
说说而已
sort of.
琳达  拿根拖布出来好吗
Hey, Linda, grab a mop, will you?
3号通道那边洒了点东西
Aisle three's got a spill-a-roosh.
这就去  有意思
Will do-a-roosh. That's fun.
宝贝  我去去就回
Okay, I'll be right back, honey.
不急
No hurry.
把那只手放那只胳膊上会怎样
What if I put that hand on that arm?
那些屁股放那些腿上呢
And those hips on those legs?
得了  蒂娜  别装上帝了
Come on, Tina, don't play God.
很危险的
It's dangerous.
那只手真美
Oh, that hand is so handsome.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
后面有人吗
Is someone back there?
也许吧  你手指怎么了
Maybe. How'd you hurt your finger?
-我家乌龟咬的  -不是吧
- My turtle bit me. - Oh, no.
是我当时太过分了
Ah, I was being a jerk.
那只乌龟只是出于本能
He was just being a turtle.
你多大了
How old are you?
我...
I'm, um...
你多大了
How old are you?
你先说
Uh, you first.
我们同时说  一  二...
We'll say it at the same time. One, two...
25岁
Twenty-five.
真的吗
Really?
-假的  我13  -假的  我14
- No, 13. - No, 14.
太好了
Cool!
所以  你喜欢巧克力味的牛奶
So... you like chocolate milk?
是
Yes.
也不是
No.
但  算是吧
But... yes.
感觉好复杂
You sound complicated.
我喜欢  可我的身体不喜欢
Well, I like it, but my body doesn't like it.
所以我在努力让我的身体喜欢上它
So I'm trying to train my body to like it.
你真勇敢
You're brave.
不是的  我有乳糖不耐症
No. I'm lactose intolerant.
都是被别人贴的标签
Labels.
老妈来短信了  我得走了
Ah. Mom's texting me. I got to go.
等等  你叫什么
Wait! What's your name?
电话呢  三围呢
Or number? Or measurements?
他走了
He's gone...
但我不会忘了他
but not forgotten.
我要用这个找到他
I'm going to use this to find him.
我在找一个男孩
I'm looking for a boy
他食指上有被乌龟咬伤的痕迹
with a turtle bite on his index finger.
是女人都在找吧
Isn't every woman?
所以  你们老妈有没有说过
So, did, uh... did your mom mention
她想回餐馆什么的
anything about missing the restaurant?
没有  她在鲜食超市好像干得挺高兴的
No, she seems happy at Fresh Feed.
也可能是因为她一直在说自己有多高兴
But maybe I just think that
我才有那样的错觉
because she kept saying how happy she is.
让她活得自在点  老爸
Let her live a little, Dad.
她只不过才脱缰了一天
She's only been off leash one day.
就是  给她些呼吸空间
Yeah, give the woman some breathing room,
你这性欲旺盛的家伙
needy-saurus rex.
*看看我*
*Look at me*
*一人搞定手推车*
*I'm wrangling these carts on my own*
*看看我*
*Look at me*
*独自切着莴苣菜*
*I'm chopping up this lettuce alone*
*我在工作*
*I'm at work*
*你能听见我在唱*
*And you can hear me sing*
*这就是工作  这就是工作*
*This is working, this is working*
-*看看我*  -*绞绞绞绞*
- *Look at me* - *Grind, grind, grind, grind*
-*我坐在这玩意上*  -*绞绞绞*
- *I'm sitting in this thing* - *Grind, grind, grind, grind*
-*启动没*  -*绞绞绞绞*
- *Is it on?* - *Grind, grind, grind, grind*
-*啦啦啦啦*  -*看看我*
- *La la la la la* -*Look at me*
-*啦啦啦*  -*她不在也没差*
- *La la la la la* - *I've barely even noticed that she's gone*
-*妈咪在工作*  -*有人在厕所*
- *Mommy is a-working* - *Someone threw up*
-*你能听见我唱*  -*吐了一地*
-*You can hear me sing* - *In the bathroom sink*
*这就是工作  这就是工作*
*This is working, this is working.*
孩子们 你们老妈
Kids, listen. Your mom...
她还是想呆在店里的  对吧
she wants to be here, right?
是啊  当然了
Oh, yeah. Of course.
-当然  -这里多好啊
- Yeah, sure. - It's so great here.
我想是吧
Uh, yeah, I think so.
你们好  我的家人们
Hello, my family.
天哪  怎么这么热
Oh, God, it's hot.
猜猜谁的第一个业绩评估得了A
Guess who aced her first performance review!
听好  琳  我有话说
Listen, Lin, uh, I want to say something.
你是想说我成绩单全A吗
Are you gonna say that I got all A's on my report card?
鲜料超市的每一项评估都是哟
In all Fresh Feed areas?
兼职还有成绩单吗  真的假的
Report cards at work? Really?
我第一周表现得了A
Yeah, I aced my first week.
他们想我做全职员工
They want me to go full-time.
还是值班经理呢
Shift manager.
你不会接受的  对吧
You're not gonna take it, right?
不会  但他们这么重视我我很高兴
No, it's just nice that they appreciate me there.
-仅此而已  -拜托  琳
- That's all. - Oh, come on, Lin.
你在这感觉不受重视吗
You're feeling underappreciated here?
有点吧
A little bit.
怎么  你也想我给你进行业绩评估吗
What, do you want me to give you a performance review?
那也未尝不可呀  鲍勃
That would be a nice start, Bob.
等等  等等  我先换个姿势
Hold on, hold on, let me get comfy.
好了  请评估你的妻子吧
And... evaluate your wife.
好吧  琳达  浴室你打扫的很干净
Okay. Uh, Linda, you clean the bathroom well.
好吧
Okay.
还知道如何更换餐巾盒
And you know how to restock a napkin dispenser.
不错啊
All right.
但你有时煲电话粥煲得很不是时候
But you're on the phone sometimes when you shouldn't be.
你从来不带发网
And you don't wear a hairnet
头发一掉就一茬
and you hair falls out a lot.
什么
What?!
你还总是偷泡菜
And you're always sneaking pickles!
但是  你
But you are, um...
说啊  老爸
Come on, Dad.
你可以的  老爸
You've got this, Dad.
你有时对人很友善
You're sometimes friendly to people.
-你说老妈吗  -对
- Oh! Mom, huh?! - Yeah.
评价很好啊
That's nice.
我才不稀罕
Not enjoying this.
不过你
Uh, but you're...
还有别的吗
Anything else?
你手总是脏兮兮的
...your hands are often dirty.
所以  10分满分的话  给你8分吧
So, you get an eight out of ten.
也许7.5分
Well, maybe a 7.5.
什么
What?!
不  是8分  绝对是8分
No, eight. Definitely an eight out of ten.
只有8分
Eight out of ten?!
鲜食超市可喜欢我了
Well, Fresh Feed loves me!
他们还给我专用的储物柜
They gave me a locker.
储物柜哦  鲍勃
A locker, Bob!
也许我该去做全职员工
Maybe I should go full-time!
好呀  祝你和你的储物柜  成绩单
Great. Have fun with your locker and your report cards
还有山寨米勒乐队生活愉快
and your Steve Miller Band cover bands.
人家有名字的
They have a name!
嘛咪嘛咪轰
The Abracadabblers.
我会的  因为那儿本来就很愉快
I will have fun! Because it's fun there!
那你赶快去呀  琳
Then go ahead, Lin.
你要是不想在这呆  就赶紧走
If you don't want to be here, then don't be here!
没有你我们也好得很
We'll be fine without you!
好  走就走
Okay, I will!
我去鲜食超市做全职员工了
I'm a full-time Fresh Feeder!
我对你的评价就是
And here's a review for you!
把枪和徽章也交出来  老妈
Uh, Dad's gonna need your gun and your badge, too, Mom.
围裙我要了  上面还有她的气味
I get her apron because it still smells like her
这味我喜欢  因为我才11岁还很恋母
and I like it because I'm 11 and I still like Mom.
好了  孩子们  晚上见
Okay, kids, I'll see you tonight.
今天我要工作一整天
I'm working a full day today.
妈妈  再见  一会我可能
Bye, Mom. I'll probably see you later
顺路闲逛到乳品冰柜区去找你
when I swing by to hang out in the milk fridge.
抱歉了  孩子们  你不能去鲜食超市
Sorry, kids. You can't go to Fresh Feed.
这需要你们
I need you here.
不
No!
你爸爸说的对  我的宝贝们
Your father's right, my babies.
你们最好留下来
You better stay here.
因为没有我  他就是一场灾难
'Cause he's a disaster without me.
不  我才不是
No, I'm not.
我开玩笑的  你不是
I'm kidding. You're not.
不是
No...
-才怪  你就是  -我没有  我
- Yes, you are! - I didn't... I...
什锦杂果
好吧  琳达
All right, Linda,
这是超市的钥匙
here are the keys to the kingdom.
十磅重的钥匙呢
Oof. Ten pounds of keys.
十磅重的乐趣哦
Ten pounds of fun!
第一天当值  都准备好了吗
You all set for your first day as shift manager?
当然  我都改头换面了
You bet! I've got my shift together.
《改头换面》[Get Your Shift Together]  史蒂夫・里佐著
一本教人们如何在生活和事业中获得成功的书
太好了
Great!
我去沼泽港放风筝
If you need me,
有事到那儿找我
I'll be in Bog Harbor with my fellow kiters.
我们晚上见
And I just mighters see you tonighters.
滚吧  格雷格
Hey, Greg, go fly a kite.
"go fly a kite"字面意思为"放风筝"  口语中也有"滚一边去"的意思
我说笑的  他是去放风筝了
I'm kidding. That's what he does.
是他的爱好嘛
That's his hobby.
我这儿没零钱了
Uh, I need quarters.
正好让我用用这钥匙  因为我是经理嘛
I'll just use my manager key. 'Cause I'm the manager.
迪斯科时间
Oh, disco minute!
经理柜台
琳达  我得写些有趣的标牌
Hey, Linda, I'm supposed to be writing funny signs,
但我没什么灵感
but I'm just not feeling it.
能让我换去冷冻区吗
You think I could switch to the frozen aisle?
好吧  我们去看看
Uh, okay. What do you say
排班表怎么样
we take a look at the shift board, huh?
排班表  排班表  你在哪
Shift board, shift board... where are you?
在这呢  好吧  我就
There you go. Okay, I'll, uh...
排班表
这样吧  我来顶你的班好了
you know what, I'll just take care of it.
多谢了  琳达
Ah, thanks, Linda.
你太有才了
You rock.
之前那份工作可没人说过我有才
Oh, hey, nobody ever said I rock at my old job,
我还得陪老板睡觉
and I was sleeping with the boss.
不是吧  你做爱技术一定很差劲
Oh, no, you must be bad at sex.
跟我一样  继续努力吧
Same boat. Keep trying.
琳达  我好像要去学校接孩子
Hey, Linda, I need to pick up my kids at school or something.
能请一天假吗
Can I cut out for the day?
当然  家人第一嘛
Of course! Family first, right?
还有  我想明天我会得病
Also, I think I'm gonna be sick tomorrow.
什么
Huh? What?
没事  明天再给你电话
Nothing. I'll call you tomorrow.
要是找不到他  怎么找我的白马王子
How can I find my dream boy if I can't find him?
振作点  小家伙
Hey, buck up, little fella.
一定找得到
This guy is findable.
我们去把这个寻人启事贴遍全镇
Let's post this "Missed connections" flyer around town.
我  一个冰柜里的怪人
me, a freak in the fridge.
你  一个手指有伤的怪人
you, a freak with a freaked-up finger.
如果你想知道我们未来有怎样的发展
"If you want to see where this can go,
请在周三下午3点到5点来开心汉堡店
"Come to Bob's Burgers Wednesday between 3:00 and 5:00 p.m.
让我们尽情做怪人吧
Freak to be you and me?"
完美
It's perfect.
好了  去贴这些海报吧
Okay, let's hang these up.
你确定不想加上"活的死的都行"这一条
You sure you don't want to add "Dead or alive"?
好主意  不过我们得弄清楚
Ooh, good point. Just so we're clear,
你是想要人家男孩还是只要他的手
you want the whole boy or just his hand?
什么都好
Whatever I can get.
杰米  幸好你在这
Jamie! Oh, thank God you're here.
听着 这些购物车交给你了
Listen, grab these shopping carts.
我还要去收银台那儿
I need to jump on a register.
能让我打个盹儿吗
Is it cool if I grab a nap instead?
我刚吃了个肉卷还喝了瓶啤酒
I just ate a meat loaf and drank a beer,
累死了
and I am wiped out.
打盹儿  不行
Grab a nap? No!
琳达经理
Manager Linda?
交货处那边有货送过来了
We got a shipment in the delivery bay.
你要去签名
You need to sign.
好  我就去  就去  不能打盹
Okay, I'm coming, coming. No nap!
-一小会儿就好  -不行
- Just a little one. - No nap!
就让眼睛休息一会儿
Just a little rest for the eyes.
-20分钟后见  -不能打盹儿
- See you in 20. - No nap!
寻人启事
我一定会找到你的
I'll find you.
在那之前千万别让伤口感染了
Until then, avoid infection.
琳达  帮个忙
Hey, Linda, cover for me?
我要像鹰一样飞离这里
I got to fly like an eagle out of here
《像鹰一样飞翔》是米勒乐队第九张录音室专辑
去参加山寨米勒乐队的排练
for a Steve Miller Band cover band rehearsal.
时间匆匆流过  流过  流过
Time keeps on slippin', slippin', slippin'.
乐队单曲《像鹰一样飞翔》中的歌词
对不起  不起  不起  我不能帮你
Well, I'm sorry, sorry, sorry, but I can't
因为我已经答应别人了
because I'm covering for someone...
谢啦
Thanks!
我让所有人都下班了吗
Did I give everyone the day off?
天哪  我得通知格雷格
Oh, God, I got to call Greg.
好耶
Yeah!
来电
开心汉堡店  我是蒂娜  你是他吗
Bob's Burgers. This is Tina. Are you him?
蒂娜  宝贝儿
Tina, sweetie!
要不要过来跟妈妈玩呀
Uh, you want to come hang out with Mommy?
这边有美味的试吃品哦
There's yummy samples.
你又准我们去鲜食超市了吗
You're allowing us back at Fresh Feed?
-我能去乳品冰柜区吗  -当然可以
- Can I go in the milk fridge? - Yeah. Yeah, sure.
乳品冰柜嘛  你可以去帮忙补货
Yeah, the milk fridge. You can restock and...
你们这儿没有购物车了
You're all out of shopping carts.
那就能拿多少买多少  老人家
Well, then just buy what you can hold, honey!
还有  把你弟弟妹妹也叫上
Oh, and, uh... bring your brother and sister.
我爱他们
I love them.
我在工作  我在工作
This is working, this is working...
老妈  你说的新试吃品在哪儿
Hey, Mom. Where's this new batch of samples?
它们是让人嘴馋呢还是让人手馋呢
Are they savory or are they crave-ory?
别管什么试吃品了
Oh, forget about the samples.
你们来帮妈妈装袋  好不好呀
You get to help Mommy bag, okay?
你骗我们
Ah, man. You tricked us.
我们要是想干活的话  待在家里就好了
If we wanted to work, we would have just stayed home.
没错  我们要是住这儿的话
Yeah, if we lived here,
这会儿就在干活儿了
we'd be at work by now.
我去乳品冰柜帮忙
I'll help in the dairy fridge.
露易丝
Louise, uh...
拿上那个标价枪去给那些金枪鱼罐头标价
grab that pricing gun and-and price those tuna cans.
1.29美元  来吧  动起来
$1.29. Okay, come on, here we go.
我只听见"拿上那个标价枪"
All I heard was "Grab that pricing gun."
德米特里  你说支票被退票了
Hey, Dmitri. My check bounced?
我们这周手头有点紧
Uh, you know, we're a little strapped this week.
我们下周再给你行吗
Is it okay if we get it to you next week?
有点紧
Little strapped?
鲍勃  你明明说你们已经严重超支了
Bob, you said you were, like, double overdrawn.
岂止是有点紧
Little strapped!
-泰迪  -好  知道了
- Teddy, shush! - Shh, yeah, right.
他挂了
Oh, he hung up.
这应该意味着不给你供肉了吧
Guess that means no meat, huh?
看来得让薯条撑全场了
Big day for fries. Right?
琳达给餐厅记的帐混乱得不行
Linda has this crazy system for our finances.
我忘记存钱了
I forgot to make the deposit,
然后就是各种讨债的人
and we got checks out all over the place.
其中包括电力公司
Including the power company.
无所谓了  反正你也没吃的要做
Doesn't matter. You don't have any food.
这样搞得我都有点想抢劫你了
You know, this kind of makes me want to loot you.
-啥  -当我没说
- What? - Never mind.
这样不是办法
This isn't working.
我得去找琳  我要关门了
I'm gonna go get Linda. I'm closing.
-你走吧  泰迪  -啥  为什么
- You got to go, Teddy. - What? Why?
停电了  又没吃的
It's dark. There's no food.
这儿什么也没有
There's nothing here for you.
-我不介意  -快点  走吧[唱吧]
- That's okay. - Go on! Scat!
不  不是  我是说
No, not...I mean...
我是让你走  不是让你唱
I meant "Go," Not "Scat."
-走  走  -不要
- Go! Go! - No!
我能去哪儿呢
Where am I supposed to go?
快走
Shoo!
出去  泰迪
Get out, Teddy!
-出去  -我真的得走了吗
- Get out! - So I should go?
你好  今天开心吗  我们服务还行吧
H-how are you? Nice day? Find everything all right?
好  好  接着
Good, good. Okay.
什么鲜食超市  长龙还差不多
Fresh Feed? More like Long Wait.
-你觉得呢  -你的收银条
- Get it? - Okay, here's your receipt.
下一个  下一个
Next in line! Next!
鸡蛋给我轻点放
Hey, careful with the eggs, huh?
我已经很轻了
This is careful.
想看看我随心所欲是什么样吗
Want to see loosey-goosey?
一堆葡萄柚倒下来把一位女士压下面了
Um, a pyramid of grapefruits fell on a lady.
-我感觉她动不了了  -什么
- I think she's trapped. - What?
吉恩  我现在提拔你为收银员
Uh, Gene, you've just been promoted to register!
我人生首次升职诶
My first promotion!
玻璃天花板  闪一边去吧
Watch out, glass ceiling!
玻璃天花板:指社会上限制妇女升任高职的无形障碍
让我看看
What are we looking at here?
香蕉  那是什么  鸡肉么
Mmm... bananas. What is that, chicken?
就给30块吧
Let's just say 30 bucks.
-30块  -好吧  5块总行了吧
- 30 bucks? - Okay, five bucks.
对不起嘛
Sorry.
下一个
Next!
你很喜欢意面嘛
Ooh, someone likes pasta.
威士忌美元  苏格兰美元
Dollar whiskey, dollar scotch,
波旁美元  裤裆美元
dollar bourbon, dollar crotch.
真便宜  要是我还喝酒就好了
Great prices! Wish I still drank!
发生什么事了
What the hell is going on here?
吉恩  你妈呢
Gene, where's your mother?
她  在附近某个地方
She's... around here somewhere.
你去家禽区那边看看
Might want to check poultry.
这东西能用吗
Does this thing work?
不知道  我新来的
I don't know. It's my first day here.
琳达  我是鲍勃
Linda? It's Bob.
咋  咋了
Wh-what?
琳  对不起  我不该装作不需要你
Listen, Lin, I'm sorry i acted like I didn't need you.
我当然需要你
Of course I need you.
我自己一个人打理不了餐馆
I can't run the restaurant by myself.
能帮我结下帐吗
Hey, can you ring me up?
不  我不是这儿的员工
No, I don't work here.
所以  琳达
So, Linda, listen...
-拜托  我就一样东西  -拿走吧
- Come on. I have one item. - Just take it.
各位  这人让我们随便拿
Hey, this guy's letting us take stuff!
免费通道
Free aisle!
好了  我可以休息了
All right, I'm going on break.
我真正想说的是
So, what I really want to tell you is...
有你在餐馆  工作才有趣
you make it fun to work at the restaurant.
我宁愿跟你一起穷困潦倒
I'd rather be scraping by together
也不想两人各自丰衣足食
than have extra money and be apart.
但如果你想体验新生活  我也可以理解
But I understand if you want to try this new life out.
虽然  我并没看出它吸引人之处
I mean... I don't really see the appeal--
这超市好脏好乱
it's a pretty nasty market--
但只要你开心  我就开心
but if it makes you happy, then it makes me happy.
那也太多了吧
Hey, come on. That's too much.
鲍勃  这里烂透了
Oh, Bob, it's awful here.
这只是一份工作
This is just a job.
这里的每个人都想翘班
Everyone who works here just wants to leave.
我受够了  我讨厌这些顾客
I hate it, and I hate the customers.
抱歉  我知道你们能听见
I'm sorry. I know you people can hear me.
我就是讨厌
I just hate it.
是能听见  因为那叫扩音器
Yeah, it's called a microphone.
-她跟我说她最讨厌的是你  -什么
- She told me she hates you the most. - What?
-鲍鲍  我想回餐馆  -琳
- Bobby, I want to come back to the restaurant. - Oh, Lin...
到5号收银台等我
Meet me at register five.
我去了
I'm on my way!
琳达
Oh, Linda.
鲍勃
Oh, Bob.
哪儿来的虾
Shrimp.
成功了
It's happening!
啥  露易丝  你做什么了
What? Louise, what did you do?
我让天上下虾了
I made it rain shrimp.
倒是你  哪样做成了
What'd you ever do?
快去接着  是沾过酱的哦
Get underneath them! They're self-dipping!
放弃吧  蒂娜  你此刻又冷又寂寞
Give up, Tina. You're cold and lonely.
你偷喝那瓶牛奶也是不对的
And you shouldn't have drank that gallon of milk.
嗨  我是冰柜里的蒂娜
Hi. I'm Tina from the fridge.
能看看你的食指吗  我不会做奇怪的事
Can I see your index finger? Nothing weird.
套上了  是你吗  你回来了吗
It fits. Is it you? Did you come back?
是的  我每周的这一天都来
I did. Every day this week.
为了我吗  还是为了来买牛奶
For me or the milk?
二者都有  我没办法不想你
For both. I can't stop thinking about you.
我想一睹真容
I want to meet face-to-face.
我  我不确定  要是见光死了呢
I-I don't know. What if we ruin what we have?
别那样说
Shh, shh. Don't say that.
-我够不着  -我来
- I can't reach. - Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
就为你的人生冒一次险吧
Take a chance for once in your life.
就算不成功  我们还有牛奶
If it doesn't work out, we'll always have the milk.
我出来了
I'm coming out.
我卡住了
I'm stuck.
我知道你只能看见一半的我
I know you can't see the other half of me,
但相信我  另一半是存在的
but trust me, it's there.
接吻  接吻  接吻  接吻
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
-我是约书  -约书亚
- I'm Josh. - Joshua...
蒂娜在干嘛
What's Tina doing?
别在冰柜里跟不认识的男孩接吻
Tina, stop kissing strange boys in the dairy fridge.
我们回家了
We're going home!
我得走了
I have to go.
这是一串号码
Here's a bunch of numbers.
看起来像是乱凑的  但其实是我的电话
They may look random, but they're my phone number.
很好  看上去很规律嘛
Cool. They look like they're in a good order.
琳达
Oh, hey, Linda.
今天的风筝飞得可起劲了
The strings were tight today, boy.
这边一切还好吧
Everything good here?
嗨  格雷格
Hi, Greg.
谢谢你给我这个机会
Thanks for taking a chance on me.
我辞职了  不过不要因此以后就不雇用
I quit, but don't let that influence hiring
即将步入中年的妇女  谢了  再见
other pre-middle-age mothers. Okay, thanks, bye.
啥  我
What? I...
我想  既然我现在
Well, I guess, now that
不在鲜食超市工作了
I don't work at Fresh Feed anymore,
我们又得紧巴巴地过日子了吧
we're back to scrimping and saving.
也许我们可以找其它赚钱的办法
Maybe we can find other ways to make some extra money.
我的收获是  凡是跟性有关的都能大卖
If there's one thing I know, it's that sex sells.
所以我们就卖跟性有关的东西好了
So all we have to do is find some sex and sell it.